<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="hello_home_second">Hello HomeSecondFragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="hello_dashboard_second">Hello DashboardSecondFragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="hello_notifications_second">Hello NotificationsSecondFragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>


    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="movie_details">More info</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="votes">votes</string>
    <string name="releaseDate">Release Date</string>
    <string name="movies">Movies\n</string>
    <string name="series">Series</string>
    <string name="movie">Movies</string>


    <string name="about" />
    <string name="about_fragment" />

    <string name="note">Add a rating out of 10</string>
    <string name="persons">List of actors</string>
    <string name="functionlObjectives">
AnneFlix, a cutting-edge streaming app, offers an extensive range of functionalities to enhance user experience. \n
Key features include: \n
- Film and Series Categories: Explore a wide array of genres, tailored to diverse viewer preferences. \n
- Films and Series Listings: Browse through an extensive collection, sorted by categories and authors, for an effortless selection process. \n
- In-depth Details: Delve into detailed descriptions for each film and series, providing a comprehensive understanding before viewing. \n
- Featured Content: Discover top picks, trending now, and editor’s choices in films and series, keeping you updated with the latest and greatest. \n
- Trailers: Watch previews of films and series, offering a sneak peek into the excitement that awaits. \n
- Favorites List: Easily mark your favorite movies and series, conveniently managed in a local database for quick access. \n
- Comments: View and share thoughts and reviews on movies and series, enhancing community engagement. \n
- About View: This section offers a thorough overview of the app's functionalities, showcases the LinkedIn profiles of our talented team members, and lists the libraries utilized in the development process.
</string>
    <string name="usedLibraries">Navigation Fragment: For efficient and intuitive app navigation.\n Hilt: Dependency Injection for streamlined and maintainable code.\n Moshi: JSON Serialization and Deserialization for seamless data handling.\n Retrofit: Consuming web services with ease and efficiency.\n Coil: Effective and memory-efficient image loading and display.\n DAllE : Generation of The Logo MBDS .</string>


</resources>